Man of God, please help me! I was shot by an armed robber.
Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for this man in the power of the Holy Ghost
and uproots whatever that is not of Jesus Christ in his life.
Glory be to God! He is free.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Good Morning, Church!
My name is Olufemi Daniel Olaegbe.
This woman by my side is my lovely wife.
I am here this morning to give thanks to the Almighty God, God of Prophet T.B. Joshua
that delivered and rescued me from the valley of the shadow of death.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was a face injury due to gunshot by armed robbers.
When I was travelling, I ran into an armed robbers' ambush, unknowingly.
There was no way for me to escape.
I don't know how God managed to take me through them.
Before I knew it, after I had driven a little distance,
I saw blood coming out - something was just pouring on my body.
When I touched my face, I realised it was shattered.
I was touching my bone - pieces of my bone - the teeth and everything.
I just kept driving until I got to a checkpoint where I met police men.
When they saw me, they were so shocked by the nature of it.
They were the ones that rushed me to the hospital.
At the hospital, I underwent many treatments and surgeries.
But after everything, the pain was still there.
Nothing could enter my mouth.
My mouth could not even hold water.
If I put water in my mouth, everything would drain out from here.
I was so worried, "Is this how I will continue to live my life?"
But I remembered that I used to watch Emmanuel TV.
I have seen a lot of things being done by Prophet T.B. Joshua in the life of people.
I summoned courage and decided to come to The SCOAN.
When I came to The SCOAN, I was opportune to be at the prayer line.
The man of God laid his hand on me.
You see that hand?
When he tapped me, I felt like my shattered jaw bone was being arranged.
Healed Of Face Injury
Due To Gunshot
I felt as if nothing had happened to me before.
I instantly felt alright.
When I got home after the healing, I felt hungry.
Whereas, I could not take anything apart from water during the time I had the problem.
But when I got home on that day, I ate.
I was surprised that I could use the jaw; the teeth could come together again.
I could eat, bite, and do everything.
Healed Of Face Injury
Due To Gunshot
Since then, up 'till this present time, I feel stronger and stronger every day.
As you see me now standing, I am 50 years old now
but I have the strength of a 25 years old boy within me.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
I said, put your hands together louder for the miracle-working God!
We give glory to God Almighty. Our brother said it all.
He said his jaw bones were shattered because of the gunshot he received at the armed robbers' attack.
But today, we just want to have a look at that same jaw.
Can we have a look?
Tell us how you are feeling as you are touching it. Do you feel any pain?
I am free.
You can see, I can touch it.
Everything is okay, there is no pain.
I feel fine.
Hallelujah. Let's put our hands together once again for Jesus!
Explain to us the pictures we are seeing on the board next to you.
Who exactly is on the pictures we are seeing?
This is me when I was at the hospital.
It was the doctors on duty that took these pictures to send to the surgeon
that they have a very severe case at hand.
Those are the pictures taken by the doctors in the first night at the hospital.
But after the prayer from Prophet T.B. Joshua,
what happened to that wound we are seeing on that picture?
After the prayer from the man of God, the wound healed.
The doctors told me that the vein that comes from here and connects to the brain cut
and they could not join it together.
The doctors then said that even if everything gets better,
there will be a drain where water will be coming out from this place.
And that I should bear in mind that that is how I am going to be living.
But after the prayer of the man of God, everything miraculously covered up.
When they saw me back at the hospital, they were asking me about it.
They said that I am a very lucky man.
As you can see now, I am fine. Everything is okay now.
We thank God Almighty because our God is a God of possibilities.
What is impossible to man is very very possible to God.
God Almighty has proven to us once again that the age of miracles has not passed.
The Miracle Worker is still alive and His name is Jesus.
If you know that, put your hands together once again for Jesus!
We give glory to God Almighty.
Good Morning, Church!
My name is Mrs Olaegbe.
My husband has said it all.
But I just want to give glory to God for saving him from death.
I couldn't believe it.
When I saw him in the hospital, it was terrible.
But I give all glory to God. Hallelujah!
Hallelujah! We give glory to God Almighty.
Viewers listening and watching me all over the world,
I want you to have faith.
Just as the man of God used to say.
Have faith in God, depend on God alone, and He will see you through.
Hallelujah! We know that with faith, all things are possible.
We give glory to God and we thank you for that wonderful word of advice.
We equally want to advise you as well
that God Almighty has healed you completely for the salvation of your soul.
So make sure you continue to follow Him along the way, making His Word the standard for your life
and His Word will continue to set you on the good road to the good life.
Once again, let us put our hands together for Jesus!
RV: Mel Flowers 16/04/2019